thisisdentistry.co.uk 2012-06-28

# Privacy Policy

THIS IS DENTISTRY has prepared this document, to help you understand how we gather and use information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

**Use of Registration Information**  
Our site’s registration area requires customers to supply contact information, such as name and e-mail address, and a query relating to your e-mail. We use this information to directly respond to your query. Information is also collected on a database to make sure that the queries we receive are dealt with professionally and also used to improve our services. E-mail data is collected on our behalf, by our database operators, but we DO NOT share any information with any third parties, so rest assured your query remains confidential.

THIS IS DENTISTRY may occasionally send you information, which we feel is relevant to your treatment or which we feel may be of interest to you. However, user may opt out of receiving further information from us at any time (See Opt Out/Opt In, below). 

**Cookies**  
THIS IS DENTISTRY does not use cookies to trace user interaction with our website.

**Use of Internet Protocol Address**  
We use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, to help identify demographic information and to analyse areas of our web page which users have or have not found useful. We may therefore combine user patterns to help improve the interaction our users have with our website. Once again this combined information is for our own use only and we DO NOT share this information with third parties. The IP address information does not identify you personally.

**Use of Demographic Information**

We also collect demographic information, obtained from internet protocol address (IP), which helps us to see who is looking and potentially interested in our services. Use of Information Collected in Promotions and Contests We may occasionally run special offers and competitions. To participate in our contests, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. THIS IS DENTISTRY uses this data to send you information about the outcome of such events. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below).

**Children’s Guidelines**  
We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information.

**Opt Out/Opt In**  
THIS IS DENTISTRY allows users to opt out of receiving e-mails from us. To opt out of our mailing list you can send an e-mail to info@thisisdentistry.co.uk

**Correct / Update Personal Information**

THIS IS DENTISTRY allows you to change or modify your personal information by sending an e-mail (See Opt Out/Opt In, above). 

**Disclaimer**  
This site contains links to other sites. THIS IS DENTISTRY is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us first by email: info@thisisdentistry.co.uk. or telephone: 020 8123 5802  
THIS IS DENTISTRY.
